Appreciate the patience
How you know what it is
But i can start for
Yeah
Help yourself
A full loanother half
So i got one full and one half got it
Hold on one second
What was the last thing you said
So i got a hot dog sonoran full forty peg
Fry
Where you pick
Two hot dogs playing one lemonade
So far you learn these got on that
And did i miss anything else
I'll run it back one more time for you
All right
Hot dog sonoran
Full porky pig
Half whiz
Half porky pig
Everything's i mean
To lemonade goes
We need snoring
Go for it
You're fine and too high
Hey
How are you guys doing that very well
Very well
Cash cards
Tap the thing
I'll line this around for you right here
Just tap that top right or insert perfect
Then it should pop up and different from
Ha ha
Then i'm gonna get the page number when it's ready
Okay perfect
Thank you
Hey guys
Don't
I dude look
I could start for you
Cash cards at the back have to play
I'll spin this around for you guys
This is gonna be page number nineteen
That'll golf when the order is ready for you
And then just tap in that top right right there
Little tip from section and then try
All right perfect
We'll get you guys once ready
Okay
You're right with you
My man
How are you guys doing today
I'm really sorry
Guys
Cash at the back
Right in front for there for you
And then see if you like it
Perfect
Here's that few when you guys are ready
Okay
Thank you
I ordered wages
That what you have on
Yep
That's my bad
After the course
Two para half of ruben
You are what you
My man
All right
Forty three half is a half
Forty six
But thank you so much
You feel very much
That's right
That's
I think that the other center
I want to come back to my
How you doing today
It's doing very well
Look like it's started for you
It works gotcha anything to drink today
Fresh squeeze
Lemonade
All right
Well
You got like that
Right there for you
Just stop right there
Then go to a tip off
All right
I'll hand you this page
We'll pay you when ready
What i'm already like right now
Oh
It's hot
Yeah
The works
Sir you got it
Guys don't like happy right there for you
You're welcome
Are you doing today
I get started for you
Just a bag
Yeah
For sure
Hi we got a treasure box out there
You can put the treasure there
You go
Yeah
Please build them
Please
You got a
Thank you
Crap order was
Are on the whole fries for two quarters
In there
There's nothing to have that got a man a great day
Yeah
Chicago sport
All right
Just tapping on top
Right right there
Then we go to a prop for you
You're welcome
I'll give you this page page
What's ready
Thanks
Two vegan chicago
One vegan
One chicago
Yeah
I'm proud
All right
We got here
One